California ephemera collection, 1860-
California Ephemera Collection,
1860-
200
Collection assembled by the UCLA Library Special Collections.
216 boxes (108 linear ft.) 5 oversize boxes. 5 oversize folders.
University of California, Los Angeles. Library Special Collections. Los Angeles, California 90095-1575
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF. Advance notice is required for access to the collection. Please contact UCLA Library Special Collections for paging information.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 4230439
Alternate Finding Aid Available
In-house card catalog is available at UCLA Library Special Collections for consultation.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of broadsides, clippings, brochures, and other ephemeral materials relating to California. Subjects include: abortion, Alcatraz Island, building and loan associations, California politics and government, Covina, drugs, Fort Ross, Greek-Americans, International Gay and Lesbian Archives, Japanese American National Museum, Hiram Johnson, William Kerckhoff, Los Angeles riots, motion picture theaters, Olympic Games, Rancho Santa Anita, Simon Wiesenthal Center, and others.
Organization and Arrangement
Collection is arranged alphabetically by subject.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Ephemera.
Container List
- Abortion - California (Boxes 190, 194)
  Box 190 is an oversize box.
- Academy Awards (Box 278)
- Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences (Box 228)
- Acting - California (Box 278)
- Acting - Study and teaching (Box 228)
- Acupuncture (Box 228)
- Adams, Ansel Easton, 1902 - (Boxes 1, 203)
  Box 203 is an oversize poster box.
- Adams, Bill, 1879 - 1953 (Box 1)
- Adamson, Bruce Campbell (Box 278)
- Admission Day (Box 1)
- Adobes - California (Boxes 1, 202)
  "Box" 202 is an oversize folder.
  - How California adobes were built in the 1830s: a simple guide to a lost art., 1978.; Item No. 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Adobes - California - Calabasas (Box 1)
- Adobes - Coronel (Antonio) Adobe - Los Angeles (Box 1)
- Adobes - Howard (Volney E.) Adobe - San Gabriel, California (Box 1)
- Adoption - California (Box 191)
- Adult education - California - Los Angeles (Box 1)
- Advertising (Boxes 228, 278)
- Advertising - California - nineteenth century (Box 219)
- Advertising - ethnic (Box 253)
  Box 197 is an oversize poster box.
- Aeroplane industry and trade (Boxes 1, 199)
  Box 199 is an oversize flat box, 18" x 23".
- African-Americans - California - Los Angeles (Boxes 191, 253, 254, 255, 278)
  - Great Black Americans: vol.1, no. 2: postcards in full color., c1993.; Item No. 1 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    Four postcards on each leaf, separated by perforations. Versos contain biographical information as do inside front cover and inside back cover. A Melrose Square Black American series special.
  - Black American Series.., 1994 calendar c1993.; Item No. 2 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    A Melrose Square Special Edition. Melrose Square Black American series.
  - The Brotherhood Crusade presents a testimonial to the pioneers of Black political leadership., 1976.; Item No. 3 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Revolutionary intercommunal day of solidarity for Bobby Seale, Erika Higgens, Angela Davis and Ruchel Magee., 1971.; Item No. 3 (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - G. O. P. sends Gold Star Mothers to France in cattle ship., 1936.; Item No. 1 (Box 254, Folder 1)
    Appears to be a reprint of a political cartoon, with added editorial comments, that previously appeared in: Metropolitan News, Chicago, Ill., Saturday Oct. 10, 1936.
  - The Appomattox Country Club: the finest Colored recreational club resort in the world., ca. 1930.; Item No. 1 (Folder 1)
    "Appomattox Country Club, 2330 Santa Ana Blvd. Phone JEfferson 9667 Los Angeles, California." Includes an inset map showing location of the Club and provides directions to the Club by both automobile and trolley. In the lower right hand corner is a "clip and mail" form to be filled out and sent into the Club for information on membership.
  - The Black Panther Manifesto: the fascists have already decided in advance to murder Chairman Bobby Seale in the electric chair., April(?) 1970.; Item No. 1 (Box 255, Folder 2)
    Includes a large image of Bobby Seale along right hand side drawn by "Emory" Issued by the Black Community News Service, the official weekly newspaper of the Black Panther Party. Published by the Black Panther Party Legal Defense Fund.
- Aged - California (Box 2)
- Aged - California - Los Angeles - Recreation (Box 228)
- Agriculture - California (Box 143)
  4 folders.
- Aguilar, Grace, 1816 - 1847 (Box 2)
- Aids (Box 228)
- Aids prevention (Box 228)
- Aids Project Los Angeles (Boxes 190, 191, 219, 225)
  Box 219 contains 2 folders.
  Box 190 is an oversize flat box.
- Air - Pollution - California (Box 2)
- Airlines - California (Box 188)
- Alameda County, California (Box 2)
- Alameda, California (Box 2)
- Albright, Horace Marden, 1890 - (Box 2)
- Alcatraz Island (Box 207)
- Alcoholics Anonymous (Box 207)
- Alcott, Carroll, 1901 - 1966 (Box 2)
- Alexander, George (Box 2)
- Alhambra, California (Box 2)
- Aliens - Illegal - California (Boxes 186, 188)
  - Busca = Search., ca. 1968 or 1969.; Item No. 1 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Caution, for your safety! [Precaucin, para su propia seguridad!]., ca. 1991.; Item No. 1 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - "Hate Christ" is the slogan of the Communists., undated.; Item No. 1 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Attention, Christians!., November 1940.; Item No. 2 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    An invitation to attend the book and author luncheon featuring Langston Hughes on November 15, 1940 at the Vista del Arroyo Hotel in Pasadena.
  - Filthee immigrants fresh off the boat., ca. 1998(?).; Item No. 2 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    Found on the sidewalk, 1st block north of Sunset Blvd. on Crescent Heights Ave. (Los Angeles), June 2, 1988.
- Allan, Maud (Box 191)
- Alliott, Hector, 1862 - 1919 (Box 2)
- Allison, George Boggs, 1904 - (Box 2)
- Alpacas (Box 278)
- Altadena, California (Box 2)
- Alturas, California (Box 2)
- Amador County, California (Box 3)
- Amargosa Opera House (Death Valley Junction, California) (Box 264)
- Amargosa, California (Box 228)
- Ambassador College. Pasadena, California (Box 3)
- American Cinematheque. Los Angeles, California (Box 278)
- American Committee for Spanish Freedom. Los Angeles Chapter. (Box 3)
- American Continental Club (Box 3)
- American Friends for Polish Unity. Los Angeles. (Box 3)
- American Historical Association. Pacific Coast Branch. (Box 3)
- American Indians (Box 278)
- American Legion. California. (Box 3)
- American newspapers - California (Box 188)
- Amoeba Music. Los Angeles, California (Box 278)
- Amtrak (Boxes 228, 278)
  3 folders.
- Amusement parks (Box 3)
- Amusement parks - California (Box 228)
- Anacapa Island, California (Box 3)
- Anaheim Angels (Baseball team) (Box 228)
- Anaheim, California (Boxes 3, 228, 278)
- Anchor Light. San Pedro, California (Box 213)
- Anderson, Frank Bolander, 1887 - (Box 3)
- Andrews, Michael, 1944 - (Box 3)
- Angel's Camp, California (Box 228)
- Animal Rescue (Box 228)
- Animal Rescue - California (Box 278)
- Animal Training - California - Los Angeles (Box 278)
- Animal Welfare (Boxes 207, 278)
- Antelope Valley, California (Box 143)
- Anthroposophical Society. Los Angeles. (Box 143)
- Antiquarian Society of California (Box 143)
  2 folders.
- Antiques - California - Exhibitions (Box 278)
- Anza-Borrego Desert State Park (Box 278)
- Anza-Borrego Desert, California (Box 264)
- Apple Valley, California (Box 264)
- Applegate Trail (Box 225)
  Box 225 is an oversize box, 15" x 19".
- Appomatox Country Club. Los Angeles, California (Box 203)
  Box 203 is an oversize flat box, poster size.
- Arab-Americans - California - Los Angeles - directories (Box 216)
- Arcadia, California (Boxes 144, 261)
  Box 261 is an oversize flat box, 21" x 25".
- Arcanian of California. Santa Monica, California (Box 207)
  June 1907 issue.
- Arcata and Mad River Railroad (Box 144)
- Arcata, California (Box 228)
- Architectural drawings - California (Box 202)
  202 is an oversize folder.
- Architectural Foundation of Los Angeles. Los Angeles, California (Box 278)
- Architectural models (Box 4)
- Architecture - California (Box 144)
- Architecture - California - Los Angeles (Box 186)
- Architecture - California, Southern (Boxes 186, 228, 278)
- Architecture, domestic - Los Angeles (Boxes 144, 199)
  Box 199 is an oversize box.
- Arlington, California - Riverside Co. (Boxes 88, 264)
- Armenian Americans - California (Box 264)
- Armenian-Americans - California - Los Angeles - directories (Box 216)
  Box 215 contains 2 folders.
- Arnold Schoenberg Institute (Box 4)
- Arrowhead, Lake (Box 4)
- Arroyo Arts Collective. Highland Park, California (Box 278)
- Arroyo Grande, California (Box 228)
- Art - Beverly Hills, California - Galleries and museums (Box 193)
- Art - California - Galleries and museums (Boxes 112, 187, 193)
  Box 193 *Also shelved oversize.
- Art - Los Angeles, California (Box 278)
- Art - Los Angeles, California - Galleries and museums (Boxes 4, 219, 227, 255, 278)
  Box 255 is an oversize flat box, 21" x 25."
- Art - Los Angeles, California - Galleries and museums (La Cienaga Blvd.) (Boxes 144, 278)
- Art - Newport Beach, California - Galleries and museums (Box 193)
- Art - Pasadena, California - Galleries and museums (Boxes 5, 207)
- Art - San Diego, California - Galleries and museums (Boxes 193, 247)
- Art - San Fernando Valley - Galleries and museums (Box 5)
  Box 5 also shelved oversize
- Art - San Francisco, California - Galleries and museums (Box 207)
- Art - Santa Barbara, California - Galleries and museums (Boxes 193, 278)
- Art - Santa Monica, California - Galleries and museums (Boxes 207, 228)
- Art - West Hollywood, California - Galleries and museums (Box 219)
- Art deco - California (Box 228)
- Artesia, California (Box 219)
- Artichokes.
  SEE: California Artichoke Advisory Board. Castroville, Calif.
- Asian-Americans (Boxes 207, 278)
- Associated General Contractors of America. Southern California Chapter. (Box 145)
- Astrology (Box 145)
- Atascadero, California (Box 188)
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railroad Company (Box 253)
- Atherton, Gertrude Franklin (Horn), 1857 - 1948 (Box 145)
- Athletic clubs - California - Los Angeles (Box 228)
- Atomic bomb shelters - design and construction (Box 6)
- Atomic energy - political aspects (Box 6)
- Auburn, California (Box 145)
- Auctions - California (Box 228)
- Audio visual equipment (Box 188)
- Austin, Alexander M, 1826 - (Box 6)
- Austin, Mary (Hunter), 1868 - 1934 (Box 6)
- Authors' Club. Los Angeles. (Box 6)
- Automatic Electric Washer SEE: Washing machines (Box 219)
- Automobile Clubs (Box 278)
- Automobile Parts (Box 278)
- Avalon, California (Box 173)
- Avery, M N, 1855? - 1942 (Box 6)
- Aviation - California (Box 6)
- Avocado industry (Boxes 6, 226)
- Axe, Ruth (Frey) (Box 6)
- Ayeroff, Loretta, 1946 - (Box 6)
- Azusa, California (Box 6)
- Bachardy, Don (Box 235)
- Baez, Joan (Box 6)
- Baja, California (Box 235)
- Baker, California (Box 235)
- Bakers and bakeries - California (Box 6)
- Bakersfield, California (Box 6)
- Balboa, California (Box 6)
- Baldwin, Elias Jackson, 1828 - 1903 (Box 6)
- Ballard, California (Box 6)
- Ballard, Charles D., 1874? - 1942 (Box 6)
- Ballona Creek (California) (Box 6)
- Ballona Wetlands Foundation. Playa Del Rey, California (Box 235)
- Balloon Route Excursion Company. Los Angeles, California (Box 6)
- Balls (Parties) (Box 6)
  Includes invitations, tickets of admissions, dance programs.
- Bancroft, Hubert Howe, 1832 - 1918 (Box 6)
- Bandini Family (Box 6)
- Bands (Music) - California - Los Angeles (Box 235)
- Banks and banking - California (Box 6)
- Banks and banking - San Francisco (Box 6)
- Banning Family (Box 145)
- Banning, California (Boxes 6, 251)
  Box 251 is an oversize box, 15" x 19".
- Bard, Thomas Robert, 1841 - 1915 (Box 145)
- Barker Brothers. Los Angeles, California (Box 263)
  Box 263 is an oversize flat box, 26-1/2" x 33-1/2".
- Barker, Eric Wilson, d. 1973 (Box 145)
- Barney's Beanery. Los Angeles, California (Box 225)
- Barrio Union for Scholastic Community Action. Los Angeles, California (Box 186)
- Barry, John Daniel, 1866 - 1942 (Box 145)
- Barstow, California (Boxes 145, 225, 278)
- Bartlett, Dana Webster, 1860 - 1942 (Box 7)
- Bartlett, Washington, 1824 - 1887 (Box 7)
- Bass Lake, California (Box 191)
- Bastanchury, Domingo (Box 7)
- Bastanchury, Maria Oxarart (Box 7)
- Bates City, California (Box 264)
- Bates Manor
  See: BATES CITY, CALIF.
- Baum, Lyman Frank, 1856 - 1919 (Box 7)
- Beaches - California, southern (Box 278)
- Bear Flag Revolt - 1846 (Box 7)
- Bear Valley, California (Box 219)
- Beatty, William Henry, 1838 - 1914 (Box 7)
- Beaumont, California (Boxes 207, 251)
- Becket, Marta (Box 264)
- Bee culture - California (Box 7)
- Bee Gees (Box 199)
- Bekins Van and Storage Co. (Box 7)
- Bel-Air Country Club. Bel-Air, California (Box 7)
- Bell, Horace, 1830 - 1918 (Box 7)
- Bell, Theodore Arlington, 1872 - 1922 (Box 7)
- Bellflower, California (Box 235)
- Benecia Arsenal, California (Box 7)
- Berkeley, California (Box 7)
- Berkeley, California - Churches (Box 7)
- Bermuda Dunes, California (Box 219)
- Bernhard, Ruth, 1905 - (Box 7)
  See shelf list for additional subject entries.
- Bernheimer Oriental Gardens. Pacific Palisades, California (Box 191)
- Beverly Hills, California (Boxes 7, 207, 225, 235)
- Beverly Hills, California - All Saints' Episcopal Church (Box 7)
- Beverly Hills, California - Beverly Hills High School (Box 145)
- Beverly Hills, California - Maps, pictorial (Box 263)
- Beyond Baroque Foundation. Venice, California (Box 145)
- Bicycling (Box 264)
- Big Basin Redwoods State Park (Box 145)
- Big Bear Lake, California (Boxes 145, 278)
- Big Bear, California (Box 264)
- Big Pine, California (Box 264)
- Big Sur, California (Box 145)
- Bigler, John, 1805 - 1871 (Box 145)
- Billington, Ray Allen, 1903 - 1981 (Box 145)
- Bimini Hot Springs. Los Angeles, California
  SEE: Hot springs - California
- Birds - California (Box 145)
- Birth control (Box 145)
- Biscailuz, Eugene Warren, 1883 - (Boxes 145, 190)
- Bishop, California (Boxes 145, 251, 279)
- Biskra, California (Riverside County) (Box 145)
- Bison (Box 264)
- Bixby, Llewellyn, 1826? - 1926 (Box 145)
- Black Guard. Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 255)
  May 23, 1968; Apr. 28, 1969, Dec. 19, 1969; Jan. 30, 1970; Mar. 20, 1970; Apr. 20, 1970.
- Black Panther Party (Box 253)
  Includes Manifesto.
- Blaisdell, James Arnold, 1867 - (Box 145)
- Bloomington, California (Box 146)
- Blueberries.
  SEE: North American Blueberry Council. Folsom, Calif.
- B'nai B'rith Record. Los Angeles, California (Box 251)
  1970 Sep.
- Boddy, Elias Manchester, 1891 - (Box 145)
- Bodega Bay, California (Box 219)
- Bohemian Club. San Francisco, California (Box 145)
- Bolsa Chica Gun Club. Long Beach, California (Box 146)
- Bolton, Herbert Eugene, 1870 - 1953 (Box 8)
- Booksellers and bookselling - California (Boxes 8, 194, 199, 235)
- Booksellers and bookselling - California - Los Angeles (Boxes 8, 196)
- Booksellers and bookselling - California - San Diego (Boxes 207, 279)
- Booksellers and bookselling - California - Southern California (Boxes 207, 235)
- Booth, Newton, 1825 - 1892 (Box 8)
- Borax - mines and mining - California (Box 235)
- Bordwell, Walter, 1855 - 1926 (Box 8)
- Boron, California (Box 235)
- Borough, Reuben W., 1883 - 1970 (Box 194)
- Borrego Springs, California (Box 8)
- Bourget Brothers. Santa Monica, California (Box 235)
- Bovard family (Box 8)
  See shelf list card for additional subject entry.
- Bowers Museum of Cultural Art. Santa Ana, California (Box 8)
- Bowling (Boxes 146, 219, 225)
- Bowron, Fletcher, 1887 - (Box 146)
- Boxing (Box 191)
- Bradbury, Ray, 1920 - (Box 8)
- Bradley, Thomas, 1917 - (Box 146)
- Braude, Marvin (Box 235)
- Brautigan, Richard, 1935 - 1984 (Box 199)
- Breast cancer - California (Box 235)
- Breast feeding (Box 264)
- Brentwood, California (Los Angeles County) (Box 146)
- Brewer, Roy (Box 146)
- Brewer, William Henry, 1828 - 1910 (Box 146)
- Brewery. Los Angeles, California (Box 207)
- Bridgeport, California (Box 264)
- Briggs, Martin Clock, 1823 - 1902 (Box 9)
- Brightfield, Myron Franklin, 1897 - 1964 (Box 9)
- Brinig, Myron, 1900 - (Box 9)
- Broadsides - Los Angeles (Box 9)
- Broadway Department Store. Los Angeles, California (Boxes 9, 251)
- Brodek, Janet Brown, collector (Box 9)
  Letters re Walter M. & Calvin Walter Brown families.
- Brower, David Rose (Box 9)
- Brown, Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald), 1905 - (Box 9)
- Brown, Edmund, Jr. (Box 188)
- Brown, John Evans, 1827 - 1895 (Box 9)
- Brown, John, 1799 - 1859 (Box 9)
  Known as Juan Flaco - additional subject entry.
- Bruce, Stewart E. (Box 9)
- Budd, James Herbert, 1853 - 1908 (Box 9)
- Buellton, California (Box 279)
- Buena Park, California (Box 9)
- Building and loan associations - California (Box 9)
- Bukowski, Charles, 1920 - (Box 9)
- Bullock, Wynn, 1902 - 1975 (Box 9)
- Bullock's. Los Angeles, California (Box 264)
- Bunche, Ralph (Box 235)
- Bundy, May (Sutton), 1888 - (Box 9)
- Burbank, California (Boxes 196, 279)
- Burbank, California - Public Library (Box 9)
- Burbank, Luther, 1849 - 1926 (Box 146)
- Burdette, Robert Jones, 1844 - 1914 (Box 146)
  See shelf list for additional subject entry.
- Burial - California (Box 146)
- Burlingame, Anson, 1820 - 1870 (Box 146)
- Burlingame, California (Box 235)
- Burnell, Charles Smith, 1874 - 1949 (Box 146)
- Burnett, Peter Hardeman, 1807 - 1895 (Box 146)
- Bus Riders Union. Los Angeles, California (Boxes 235, 253)
  Oversize poster.
  Box 253 is an oversize poster box.
  - Fare strike begins today: no seat? no fare! [Huelga de tarifa empieza hoy: no asiento? no pago!]., 1998.; Item No. 1 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Hey NFL! don't play ball with a racist city [Oye NFL! no jueges pelota con una ciudad racista]., 1999.; Item No. 1 (Box 253, Folder 2)
- Bus Riders Union. Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 253)
  Poster.
- Business - California - directories (Box 188)
- Business cards - Los Angeles (Box 191)
- Business enterprises - California (Box 147)
- Business enterprises - Los Angeles (Boxes 10, 147, 188)
- Business enterprises - Orange County, California (Box 147)
- Business enterprises - San Francisco (Boxes 147, 202)
  Folder 202 is an oversize folder.
- Butte County, California (Box 148)
- Butterfield and Butterfield. Los Angeles. (Box 207)
- Butterfield Trail (Box 148)
- Cable television (Boxes 208, 235)
- Cabrillo National Monument. Point Loma, California (Box 148)
  Subject entry for Point Loma.
- Cabrillo, Juan Rodriguez, d. 1543 (Box 148)
  Subject entry for portrait.
- Cadman, Charles Wakefield, 1881 - 1946 (Box 148)
- Cain, James Mallahan, 1892 - (Box 148)
- Cain, Paul, pseud., 1902 - 1966 (Box 148)
  Cross references: 1.Ruric, Peter 2.Sims, George
- Cajon Pass, California (Box 148)
- Calaveras County, California (Box 148)
  See shelf list for added entries.
- Calexico, California (Box 11)
- Calico, California (Box 11)
- Caliente, California (Box 219)
- California - Bicentennial - 1969-1970 (Boxes 197, 264)
  Box 197 is an oversize box.
  - Discover downtown L.A.: a 200th birthday gift to Los Angeles for children of all ages to explore and enjoy., c1981.; Item No. 1 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    Includes an inset view of the Los Angeles basin from downtown to Santa Monica Bay featuring the region's freeways. Important commercial and cultural buildings are numbered on the view and illustrations of these buildings along with textual information are featured on the verso of the view. "Look up! Look up! Look up!"--Along upper left had side of view. Includes some historical facts about Los Angeles.
  - Bicentennial Summer FestivaLA Calendar., c1981.; Item No. 2 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    LA's the Place (trademark) "Los Angeles Bicentennial 1781-1981" Drawings and seating plans by Access Press, Inc.
- California - Biography (Box 11)
- California - Centennial celebrations, etc. (Box 11)
  Box 11 contains 3 folders.
  - Death Valley centennial celebration., December 1949.; Item No. 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Broadside advertising an outdoor theatrical production entitled, "The Death Valley '49ers." The play is a re-enactment of the Manly-Jayhawkers Expedition across Death Valley in 1849.
  - San Fernando Fiesta, Inc. presents: "Recuerdos de San Fernando Rey"., June 1948.; Item No. 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Flier advertising the 14th annual fiesta in honor of the 151st anniversary of the founding of the San Fernando Mission.
- California - Central Coast (Box 265)
- California - Climate (Box 148)
- California - Consumer education (Box 13)
- California - Description - poetry (Box 148)
- California - Description and travel (Boxes 113, 114, 213, 236, 252, 261, 279)
  Poster for California Is Calling You by KD and Gary F. Kurutz. Box 113 contains 4 folders.
  Box 261 is an oversize flat box, 21" x 25". Box 252 is an oversize flat box, 21" x 25"
- California - Description and travel - Route 395 (Box 225)
- California - Economic conditions (Box 148)
  - Great Negro tide surges into melting pot of west; P. 3-4 in California: promise and problems.., September 17, 1962.; Item No. 1 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    This copy of the Los Angeles Times article entitled "Great Negro tide surges into melting pot of west" is taken from a pamphlet entitled "California: promise and problems." Other articles in the pamphlet discuss issues such as population and economic growth in the Los Angeles area.
- California - Gold discoveries (Box 148)
- California - History (Boxes 14, 15)
  6 folders.
- California - Hotels, taverns, etc. (Box 219)
- California - Maps (Boxes 214, 236)
- California - Maps - tourist (Box 188)
- California - Maps, pictorial (Box 263)
- California - Politics and government (Boxes 115, 191)
- California - Politics and government - 1863 - 1967 (Box 115)
- California - Politics and government - 1867 - 1871 (Box 115)
- California - Politics and government - 1871 - 1875 (Box 115)
- California - Politics and government - 1883 - 1887 (Boxes 115, 197, 200)
  Folder 200 is an oversize folder.
- California - Politics and government - 1891 - 1895 (Box 115)
- California - Politics and government - 1895 - 1899 (Box 115)
- California - Politics and government - 1899 - 1903 (Box 115)
- California - Politics and government - 1903 - 1907 (Box 115)
- California - Politics and government - 1907 - 1911 (Box 115)
- California - Politics and government - 1911 - 1917 (Boxes 115, 199)
- California - Politics and government - 1917 - 1926 (Box 215)
- California - Politics and government - 1927 - 1930 (Box 215)
- California - Politics and government - 1931 - 1934 (Box 215)
- California - Politics and government - 1934 - 1939 (Box 215)
- California - Politics and government - 1943 - 1953 (Box 116)
- California - Politics and government - 1953 - 1959 (Box 116)
- California - Politics and government - 1959 - 1969 (Boxes 116, 279)
- California - Politics and government - 1970 (Boxes 116, 203)
- California - Politics and government - 1971 (Box 117)
- California - Politics and government - 1971 - 1974 (Box 117)
- California - Politics and government - 1972 (Box 117)
- California - Politics and government - 1973 (Box 117)
- California - Politics and government - 1974 (Box 200)
- California - Politics and government - 1975 (Box 117)
- California - Politics and government - 1976 (Box 118)
- California - Politics and government - 1977 (Box 118)
- California - Politics and government - 1978 (Box 118)
- California - Politics and government - 1979 (Box 118)
- California - Politics and government - 1980 (Box 119)
- California - Politics and government - 1981 (Box 119)
- California - Politics and government - 1982 (Box 119)